{
    "subject": "resource/Langenthal",
    "predicate": "ontology/twinTown",
    "object": "resource/Neviano",
    "human_readable": "Langenthal has a twin town called Neviano.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886454343795776,
            "question": "Is Neviano a twin town of Langenthal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9601927995681763,
            "question": "Name a town that is twinned with Langenthal."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8910444378852844,
            "question": "What is the name of Langenthal's twin town?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7947186827659607,
            "question": "What relationship exists between Langenthal and Neviano?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6602299213409424,
            "question": "Are Langenthal and Neviano connected through a special agreement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49769461154937744,
            "question": "Does Langenthal have a partner city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48694559931755066,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a relationship between Langenthal and another town?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48085567355155945,
            "question": "What is the name of Langenthal's partner city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4295109212398529,
            "question": "Which two towns are considered twins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32308229804039,
            "question": "Besides Langenthal, what other town has a twinning agreement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Langenthal has a twin town called Neviano.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5762_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which two towns are considered twins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5762_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Langenthal's partner city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5762_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a relationship between Langenthal and another town?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5762_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5762_3.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Langenthal, Switzerland, was twinned with Neviano, Italy, in 2001. This supports the statement that Langenthal has a twin town called Neviano."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}